Sui, does that mean you were confessed to?
With the intent of marriage?
I think so.
He's once divorced already, but...
You've never wanted a child yourself?
Although my older brother
took up the family mantle,
he was always pressured to have an heir.
As a result,
I decided I wanted no children in my life.
Which is partially why I think he chose me.
And you're okay with this?
I don't think I'll meet
an individual like him again.
Someone who choses me,
while knowing my circumstances.
I see.
Then you think he's good for you, too?
I'm definitely considering his offer.
I've watched what you've gone through.
So, I want you to become happy, okay?
Thanks.
Say, did your sister tell you her secret?
Her secret?
I heard your due date is coming up.
They'll be Sui's niece or nephew, right?
I'm sorry, who are you?
How do you know my sister?
And what secret?
Is Sui genuinely excited for your child?
She couldn't be.
She must be so jealous you're pregnant.
Excuse me?
What are you...
You're the one who wanted to hear her secret.
Huh?
Sui is infertile.
That's why Himukai
broke off their engagement.
She won't ever attain a happiness like yours.
I truly feel sorry for her.
Sui is...
Infertile?
Let's make sure our kids
become best friends, okay?
Are you not interested in having kids?
Sui, I'm always here for you, okay?
Promise me you'll take your marriage
and future kids seriously.
"On her side"?
I'm the worst.
I hurt Mizuno, and now...
I never had any right to love someone.
Here.
That's enough moping
and drowning in alcohol for you.
Mao. What're you gonna do about Sui?
You love her, don't you?
You can't trick me.
How long do you think I've known you?
Actually...
I think right now,
I need to focus on reorienting myself.
I have to be more honest with myself.
Honest with yourself, huh?
Well, that's not half bad either.
Whatever you do, don't regret it, okay?
A design contest?
Yeah. I want to do this, now.
Where'd your motivation come from?
Our team is especially busy now,
so this is a real inopportune time...
This is more for my sake,
so I'll handle the details myself.
If you're asking why now, well...
Let's just say I want to put in
the effort, for once.
A winning design
would certainly help your career, sure.
But don't major firms
usually win this contest?
Yeah.
But the town they're asking for
aligns with the design of my dreams.
I know it won't stand a chance now.
But one day, I will build something like this.
Which is why I want to take action, now.
I only wanted to tell you all
I'd be participating.
I won't cause you all extra trouble.
"Extra trouble"...
Personally, I'd want you to rely on me.
Huh?
Challenging yourself
is far more important than the end result.
So, I want to help you in that endeavor.
She's right. Don't count us out.
Exactly. You wouldn't be troubling us.
You all helped me when I first arrived.
It's the least I can do to help.
Let's all help Mao, together.
Right?
Don't know how I can help,
but yeah, I'll do what I can.
So noncommittal.
- So judgemental.
- Me?
How so?
It's in your character.
Wow, rude.
You're judgemental personified.
You have gone too far.
Matsubara.
I'm sorry.
Mizuno and I... we...
She dumped you, didn't she?
Huh?
What?
Wait, seriously?
I was joking.
Yeah. Dead serious.
I see.
So, Nana actually...
Matsubara.
I...
If you dumped her, I would've slugged you.
Guess that explains
your sudden motivation, though.
Yeah. But that's not the only reason.
Good luck to the both of us then?
Yeah. Thanks.
Nana, the water. It's overflowing.
Huh?
Sorry, I was spacing out.
Thank you.
Here.
Huh?
You like the chocolates
from this place, right?
Sorry, it's about all I can do to help.
Matsubara.
I love it.
Huh?
These chocolates. I do love them.
Oh.
The chocolates.
Thanks.
What are you doing now?
I'm drafting up a potential clientele pool.
Is there any way I can help?
I could gather some documents
on additional land plots?
Thanks, that'd really help.
Had you planned to join
this design contest beforehand?
No. But when I think about leaving,
and going independent one day,
I realize taking on these challenges
and having accomplishments will help.
Independent?
I can't rely on Uncle...
I mean, Mr. Hoshina forever.
I want him to know I'll be okay on my own.
I see.
Everything okay?
Yup.
I'll get those documents to you, ASAP.
So, Mao will leave the office one day.
Hello?
Sorry to call out of the blue.
I considered sending a text,
but I wanted to hear your voice.
Huh?
Monou.
Are you free this upcoming Sunday?
I am, yes.
Would you like to join me
for lunch at Ruby-On?
They recently got a fresh shipment
of winter oysters.
I love oysters.
Thank you for the offer.
I look forward to joining you.
If possible,
I'd like to hear your reply as well.
All right.
Then I'll see you Sunday.
You're... Tsukidome?
I apologize for visiting
without an appointment.
The contest run by Noval Inc., huh?
Yes. The one you won
in your second year as an architect.
You did your research.
I should still have my designs around here...
Maybe it's in this drawer.
Found them.
Feel free to use them as reference.
Huh? You wouldn't mind?
You clearly have the passion,
and you're my junior.
It's the least I can do to help.
Thank you.
Good luck with the contest.
I might have other drafts I can lend you...
I'm glad you're there for her, Hirose.
Huh?
I mean...
I'm sorry, that came out of nowhere.
Please make Sui...
Monou, happy.
This really did come out of nowhere.
Monou will always try
to solve her problems on her own.
She's a person with real strength.
But...
She's also gone through a lot of strife.
Even so,
she lives to her fullest, doing all she can.
So...
Please, make her happy.
And you're okay with that?
Yes.
Tsukidome.
There's one thing you're wrong about.
Huh?
Of course, I do wish to make Sui happy.
However...
My feelings alone won't bring her happiness.
How she feels is equally,
if not more important to the equation.
- Welcome back.
- Welcome home.
Welcome.
Ouch...
Someone...
Please... help me...
Thank you.
Thank you for always visiting.
Of course.
Enjoy.
I enjoyed lunch today.
I'm glad.
- So...
Sorry.
Likewise, sorry.
Go ahead.
I wanted to reply to your...
I'm so sorry.
Huh?
[Shinya Ioka]
Don't mind me, take it.
Thank you.
Hello?
Sui!
Shinya?
Rin collapsed. She was taken to the hospital.
What?
Rin!
Sui...
Shinya's talking to the doctor now.
Thank god.
You're both safe...
Sui...
Everything will be okay.
Shinya will be back soon.
No, Sui.
I'm so sorry.
I'm getting what I deserve.
I said so much without knowing anything...
What are you talking about?
Sui, your body.
I heard what happened.
Your old coworker told me.
Takizawa...
Rin.
You're not, "getting what you deserve."
Focus on your baby, okay?
Rin.
I can't wait to meet your baby.
I've been so, so excited for this moment.
Really?
Ow...
Rin? Rin! Are you okay?
Rin!
Because the baby remains put,
we'll be performing an emergency C-section.
I'll be removing your stomach pad.
Okay.
Hang in there.
Rin.
I promise you'll be okay.
We'll be moving her.
- Ready?
- Yes.
I heard a passerby helped Rin
when she collapsed.
I'll buy you a drink.
Be right back.
Sui?
I need to ask you a question.
I decide my own happiness.
You truly are an honest individual.
I want to become happy,
regardless of whether or not I can do it.